iraniansingles.com 2018-06-29

# Untitled Document

Webico Enterprise ("Webico") is committed to protecting your personal information as part of the iraniansingles.com dating site . This privacy statement only applies to activities and transactions in which you do on our website where data gathered on the Webico Websites and email between Webico members. This privacy policy may periodically be modified. Each time you visit or logon the Site or provide Webico with information, you are agreeing and accepting the privacy policy. You must be of minimum age of 18 to use this site.

As part of a dating site, you agree to provide information about you to Webico such as: 

Only include your private information such as email address or passwords in the appropriate sections. Do not include private information in the public profile sections.

Webico may link with other third party companies to provide services and products which you may click on our site. Webico does not control the business practices of such third parties and this privacy policy does not apply to such third parties. Webico allows for third party companies to server ads and collect anonymous information (click, browser type, date, time) during your usage.

Based on industry best practices, Webico automatically collects your IP address and the web page from which you came. This IP information can used for IT troubleshooting and to gather broad demographic information.

Webico uses session cookies which are required to identify users as they move from one page to another.   
Information regarding profiles you have viewed will be considered public information and share with the user that has been viewed. This is an effort to improve the communication and “break the ice” between users. 

Your email is used to help us effectively communicate with you in connection with your transactions and other activities on the site, including, but not limited to messaging, passwords, billing information, updates, and members contacts and special Webico promotions or discounts. 

By registering, you are agreeing to receive from time to time receive email communication or banner ads or similar from sponsored third parties. 

Any third party with whom is authorized to use your personal information in accordance with our contractual arrangements with such third parties and in accordance with their own privacy policies, over which we have no control, and you agree that we are not responsible or liable for any of their actions or omissions. You will be responsible for your personal privacy information for anyone who you choose to contact.  
 Webico uses credit card information to bill for your subscription through a third party processor. By making a purchase transaction, you agree to allow Webico to provide your financial information to other service providers to support and process your activities and transactions, as well as to your credit card issuer for their purposes.   
These third parties may include the credit card companies, banks, and intermediary financial processors. By purchasing, or registering for services, you to submit financial information in order to use them, you also consent to Webico providing your financial information to those third parties. 

Webico may be required to disclose personal information to local or federal law enforcement officials in order to protect other members or Webico. Your personal information or financial information may be passed on to a third party in the event of change of ownership.   
Webico may review all demographic information and profile information. It may use public information to make a match with another member and communicate that via the browser or email.   
Webico may use profile information to customize the content provided to you.  
Webico may also share demographic information with advertisers such Google Ads.  
Webico uses secure server software (SSL) for secure commerce transactions.  
Webico may update its privacy policy at any time without notice where the information will be available in the Privacy section. Please review the Privacy section for latest  
You can opt-out of our services provided by either deleting or hiding your profile.  
You can opt-out from our mailing list, by clicking on account preferences.

If you have questions or concerns regarding privacy, don’t’ hesitate to email or call us  
Webico Enterprises  
iraniansingles.com   
575 Anton Blvd Suite 300-125  
Costa Mesa, Ca. 92626  
949-387-6166
